<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
  <rss version="2.0"><channel> 
				<title>RSS  MediaVerse </title> 
				<description>A modern web application built as a learning and portfolio project, focusing on clean architecture, responsive design, and practical functionality.</description>
				<link>https://www.MediaVerse.com</link> 
				<language>id-id</language><item>
						                <title>Health ministry warns of rising flu cases ahead of rainy season</title>
						                <link>http://localhost/MediaVerse/berita/detail/health-ministry-warns-of-rising-flu-cases-ahead-of-rainy-season</link>
						                <description>The health ministry issued an alert on Thursday after a rise in flu cases was recorded in several regions.
Officials advise citizens to practice hygiene measures and seek early treatment when symptoms appear.
The ministry also urged high-risk groups to get vaccinated.</description>
					                </item><item>
						                <title>New study links consistent sleep patterns to improved mental health</title>
						                <link>http://localhost/MediaVerse/berita/detail/new-study-links-consistent-sleep-patterns-to-improved-mental-health</link>
						                <description>Researchers have found that maintaining a consistent sleep schedule significantly improves mental well-being.
The findings highlight the need for better sleep hygiene among adults and teenagers.
Experts recommend reducing screen time before bed to improve sleep quality.</description>
					                </item><item>
						                <title>New sci-fi film breaks streaming records within first 24 hours</title>
						                <link>http://localhost/MediaVerse/berita/detail/new-sci-fi-film-breaks-streaming-records-within-first-24-hours</link>
						                <description>A newly released sci-fi film has shattered streaming platform records, drawing millions of viewers in a single day.
The film's strong visuals and storyline received widespread praise from critics and audiences alike.
producers announced plans for a sequel next year.</description>
					                </item><item>
						                <title>Popular singer announces world tour dates for 2026</title>
						                <link>http://localhost/MediaVerse/berita/detail/popular-singer-announces-world-tour-dates-for-2026</link>
						                <description>A globally acclaimed singer has revealed official dates for a massive world tour scheduled for 2026.
Fans across Asia, Europe, and North America will have the chance to attend the highly anticipated concerts.
Tickets are expected to sell out within hours once released.</description>
					                </item><item>
						                <title>Regional leaders meet to discuss 2026 security cooperation framework</title>
						                <link>http://localhost/MediaVerse/berita/detail/regional-leaders-meet-to-discuss-2026-security-cooperation-framework</link>
						                <description>Leaders from multiple provinces gathered on Thursday to discuss a new security cooperation plan for 2026.
The meeting focused on joint intelligence sharing, border monitoring, and emergency response coordination.
Officials say the framework could be finalized by March 2026.</description>
					                </item><item>
						                <title>Parliament debates new transparency bill amid rising public pressure</title>
						                <link>http://localhost/MediaVerse/berita/detail/parliament-debates-new-transparency-bill-amid-rising-public-pressure</link>
						                <description>The national parliament opened discussions on a new transparency bill aimed at increasing public access to government data.
The proposal has gained strong support following months of public demand for greater accountability.
Lawmakers are expected to vote on the bill early next year.</description>
					                </item><item>
						                <title>Indonesia’s digital banking sector sees record growth in Q4</title>
						                <link>http://localhost/MediaVerse/berita/detail/indonesias-digital-banking-sector-sees-record-growth-in-q4</link>
						                <description>Indonesia’s digital banking platforms reported a record surge in new users during Q4 2025.
Financial experts attribute the rise to improved mobile services and increased public trust in online banking systems.
Regulators expect the sector to continue expanding rapidly through 2026.</description>
					                </item><item>
						                <title>Global oil prices fall as demand slows heading into 2026</title>
						                <link>http://localhost/MediaVerse/berita/detail/global-oil-prices-fall-as-demand-slows-heading-into-2026</link>
						                <description>Global oil prices dropped nearly 3% on Thursday as demand indicators showed signs of weakening toward the end of 2025.
Analysts say slowing industrial output in several major economies contributed to the decline, raising concerns about market stability.
Energy firms remain cautious as they prepare for potential volatility in early 2026.</description>
					                </item><item>
						                <title>Real Madrid close to securing €85m midfielder as January transfer window approaches</title>
						                <link>http://localhost/MediaVerse/berita/detail/real-madrid-close-to-securing-85m-midfielder-as-january-transfer-window-approaches</link>
						                <description>Real Madrid are reportedly finalizing negotiations to sign a highly rated European midfielder in an €85 million deal ahead of the January transfer window.
Spanish media outlets claim the club has reached an agreement in principle with the player, who has been on Carlo Ancelotti's radar since last season.
The midfielder is expected to complete medical tests in the coming weeks, with the official announcement anticipated before the winter market opens.
If completed, the signing would add significant depth to Madrid's midfield and strengthen their long-term project as they continue their push for La Liga and Champions League success.</description>
					                </item><item>
						                <title>Manchester City confirm star striker sidelined for six weeks with ankle injury</title>
						                <link>http://localhost/MediaVerse/berita/detail/manchester-city-confirm-star-striker-sidelined-for-six-weeks-with-ankle-injury</link>
						                <description>Manchester City have confirmed that their leading striker will be out of action for at least six weeks following an ankle injury sustained during training on Wednesday.
The club released a statement saying the medical team has advised a full rehabilitation program, ruling the player out of City's upcoming Premier League and Champions League fixtures.
Pep Guardiola expressed concern but remained optimistic about the striker's recovery timeline, stating that the squad will adapt and push forward despite the setback.
The injury comes at a crucial stage of the season as City continue to compete on multiple fronts, increasing pressure on the remaining forwards in the squad.</description>
					                </item></channel>
  	</rss>